Willy Prado

Frontend Developer

I'm Willy Prado, web developer. I started my studies (selftaught) in web development in June 2019 and I have gained experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React among others(WordPress). I also have more than 5 years of experience in digital marketing; I love read manhua, eat chocolate, watch anime and draw. Co-organizer of Reactlaconf & Friends of Figma Medellin.





🔽 pradopublicity@gmail.com



Barcelona, Spain.



willyprados



+34 685 63 62 89

Experience

Mar. 2023 - Jun. 2023

Rica Design Frontend Developer

- I development projects for Cinergia, Flappin, others, using Laravel, PHP, Docker, Vue, Tailwind, SASS.

Aug. 2022 - Jan. 2023

Freelancer Frontend Developer

- I worked as a freelancer for some clients in Italy and the USA, developing websites in CMS like WordPress.

Nov. 2021 - May. 2022

Nivelics SAS Frontend Developer

- I development projects for Televisa (Web Streaming) using Next.js & Styled Component. I also give monthly talks on some topics of interest to the team.

Jun. 2021 - Nov. 2021

Click2Action Frontend Developer

- I development projects from scratch (e-commerce, web pages, moodle) using HTML, CSS, Javascript, React.js and WordPress.
- Implementation of new work tools in the company (Slack, Trello, Mautic, Figma, among others).

Aug. 2020 - Apr. 2021

Zero Azul Agency Frontend Developer

- I development projects from scratch (emails, digital magazines, web pages) using HTML, CSS, Javascript, React.js and WordPress.

Formation

2011 - 2016

Universidad de Carabobo

Literature

Skills

Javascript - React - Netx.js - Git - CSS - SCSS - Tailwind - Material UI - Styled Component - HTML - Figma.

Language

Spanish (Native) English A2 (Learning at Number 16 School)

Projects

Kibus Page 🕜

Jr Developer technical test project for Rocket Digital company. Built on Vite.js, React.js with Style Components. https://github.com/willyprados/kibus-<u>prueba</u>

LineaVIVA Edition 133

"Linea VIVA" magazine for the month of December 2020. Magazine created in HTML, CSS and some Javascript. https://github.com/willyprados/ISAGENamazine-133

Website Personal 🔗



Personal website, built from scratch with the guidance of a tutor. Final project of a bootcamp in Medellín Colombia called "Frontend Bootstrapping". For the construction of this site use vanilla Javascript, html and css.